League of Women Voters of Albany County; Records apap128
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Local Program Studies, 1948-1999; 3; 2.69 cubic ft.
  - Solid Waste Management, Incineration Consensus, 1989 (Box 11 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 23)
  - Solid Waste Management, Incineration Study, 1989-1991 (Box 11 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 24)
  - Solid Waste Management, Incineration Study Material, 1986-1990 (Box 11 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 25-26)
  - Solid Waste Management, Incineration Study Material, 1988; 1990-1992 (Box 11 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 27)
  - Solid Waste Management, Incineration Study Material, 1987; 1988; 1991 (Box 11 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 28)
  - Solid Waste Management Study Material, 1989-1991 (Box 11 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 29)
  - Smart Growth in Albany County, 2000 (Box 12 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 1)
  - Smart Growth in Albany County, 2000-2001 (Box 12 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 2)
  - Title IX Study, Albany High School and Bethlehem Central Schools, 1989 (Box 12 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 3)
  - Unit Meetings, Guidelines for Local Study Groups, 1949-1955; 1957; 1964-1970; 1973 (Box 12 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 4)
  - Unit Meetings, Local Study Group Topics, 1964-1970 (Box 12 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 5)
    Including Apportionment, Education, Housing, Human Resources, Judiciary, Voter Service, and Welfare.
  - Water Resources Study, 1956-1960 (Box 12 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 6)
  - Albany Building Code Study, 1948; 1963 (Box 39 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 8)
  - Albany County Mental Health Study, 1955-1956; 1958; 1965 (Box 39 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 9)
  - Financing Education, LWV, 1960-1962 (Box 39 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 10)
  - Frustration...Without Equal Representation, ca. 1963 (Box 39 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 11)
  - Libraries for Albany County Knocking, Undated (Box 39 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 12)
  - Open Meeting Committee, Surveys, 1980 (Box 39 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 13)
  - Redistricting, County-wide Question Number 1 and Amendment, Proposed by LWVAC President, 1965 (Box 39 (3-Local Program Studies), Folder 14)
- Albany County Government, 1953-2000; 4; 1.13 cubic ft.
  Many of the local items of study the LWVAC took on dealt with the Albany County Government and its departments and are included in this series. The majority of this series is made of material related to the Albany County Charter revision in 1973 and again in 1993. There are Albany County Charter Revision Committee meeting minutes, press releases, and public hearing testimony by members of the LWVAC. The Albany County Legislature was another focus of the LWVAC; the group lobbied for and against certain county issues in the 1970s and 1990s. Also in this series are the guides to Albany County the LWVAC published. Spotlight on Albany County was first published in 1955. The subsequent This is Albany County was published in 1968, 1971, 1980, and 1996.
  - Albany County Board of Health, 1993 (Box 13 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 1)
  - Albany County Budget Audits, 1995 (Box 13 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 2)
  - Albany County Charter, 1973-1974 (Box 13 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 3)
  - Albany County Charter Citizens Review Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 13 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 4)
  - Albany County Charter News Clippings, 1973-1975 (Box 13 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 5)
  - Albany County Charter Revision Committee, 1992 (Box 13 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 6)
    April 1992 Draft of the Albany County Charter (includes letters to the editor of the Times Union and the.
  - Albany County Charter Revision Committee, 1992 (Box 13 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 7)
    (includes testimony of LWVAC before the County Legislature, report of the Management Advisory Commission for Albany County, and correspondence).
  - Albany County Charter Revision Committee, 1993 (Box 13 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 8)
    (includes establishment of Albany County Charter Revision Commission, the Commission's Report, and the August 1993 Draft of the Albany County Charter).
  - Albany County Charter Revision Committee, 1993 (Box 13 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 9)
    (includes financial campaign for LWVAC flyer in support of Charter Revision).
  - Albany County Charter Revision Committee, 1993 (Box 13 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 10)
    (includes LWVAC proposals for charter revision).
  - Albany County Charter Revision Committee, 1993-1994; 1995 (Box 14 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 1)
    (includes committee meeting minutes, press releases, and public hearing testimony by LWVAC).
  - Albany County Charter Revision Coroner Study, 1993-1994 (Box 14 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 2)
  - Albany County Charter Revision News Clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 14 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 3)
  - Albany County Charter Revision News Clippings, 1992-1995 (Box 14 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 4)
  - Albany County Departments, 1953-1954 (Box 14 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 5)
    Public Welfare 1953; Civil Defense, 1954; Justice, 1954; Public Works, 1954.
  - Albany County Government News Clippings, 1975-1995 (not inclusive) (Box 14 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 6)
  - Albany County Government News Clippings, 1992-2000 (not inclusive) (Box 14 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 7)
  - Albany County Legislation, LWVAC Action, 1973; 1975; 1976 (Box 14 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 8)
  - Albany County Legislation, LWVAC Action, 1991; 1995; 1996 (Box 14 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 9)
  - Albany County Legislation, LWVAC Action, 1995-1997 (Box 15 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 1)
  - Albany County Legislative District Maps, Undated (Box 15 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 2)
  - Albany County Legislative Watch, 1994-1995 (Box 15 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 3)
  - Albany County Management Advisory Committee Report, 1992 (Box 15 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 4)
  - Albany County Management and Productivity Study, 1995 (Box 15 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 5)
  - Citizens for a County Executive, 1971-1975 (Box 15 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 6)
  - Round Table on Albany County Fiscal Condition, 1993 (Box 15 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 7)
  - Spotlight on Albany County, 1955 (Box 15 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 8)
  - This is Albany County, 1968 (Box 15 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 9)
  - This is Albany County, 1971 (Box 15 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 10)
  - This is Albany County, 1980 (Box 15 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 11)
  - This is Albany County, 1996 (Box 15 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 12)
  - This is Albany County, 2000 (Box 15 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 13)
  - Albany County Charter, 1993 (Box 40 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 1)
  - Albany County Charter Revision Commission Program Committee, ca. 1993 (Box 40 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 2)
  - Albany County Legislative Watch, 1992 (Box 40 (4-Albany County Government), Folder 3)
- Study and Action, 1952-2000; 5; 7.14 cubic ft.
  In addition to Voter Service, the LWV focuses on informing citizens about various topics of concern through study and action. This series contains materials related to public policy issues that are broader in scope than the Local Program Studies. The LWVAC takes part in studies and lobbies on a wide range of topics pertaining to the state and national LWV programs. Subjects in this series include state issues such as court reform in New York State (1955-1994), the New York State Constitutional Convention in 1967 and 1997, and Universal Health Care for New York State (1989-1992). National items include International Relations (1954-1998), which concerns United States foreign policy on trade, development assistance, the United Nations, and National Security (1982-1985). The environment and financing education were also topics of study. Materials under the heading "Legislative Action" include calls for action, memos, statements at public hearings, and correspondence to and from legislators relating to items the LWV lobbied for or against (1952-1999). Also in this series are materials on lobbying techniques.
  - Action Packets, 1986 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 1)
  - Advocacy Conference, 1992 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 2)
  - Advocacy Conference, 1993 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 3)
  - Advocacy Conference, 1994 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 4)
  - Agriculture Study, 1987-1988 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 5)
  - Art of Advocacy Conference, 1996 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 6)
  - Art of Advocacy Conference, 1997 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 7)
  - Art of Advocacy Conference, 1998 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 8)
  - Apportionment, 1961-1965 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 9)
  - Apportionment, 1966; 1969 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 10)
  - Apportionment, Newsletters, News Clippings, and Pamphlets, 1961-1966 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 11)
  - Breast Cancer, 1994-1996 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 12)
  - Campaign Finance, 1972; 1974; 1978 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 13)
  - Campaign Finance, 1996-1997 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 14)
  - Campaign Finance, News Clippings, 1989-1991 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 15)
  - Charter Schools Study, 1999 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 16)
  - Charter Schools Study, 1999-2000 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 17)
  - Children at Risk, 1994 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 18)
  - Continuing Responsibilities, 1953-1958 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 19)
  - Continuing Responsibilities, 1960-1964 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 20)
  - Continuing Responsibilities, 1965-1968 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 21)
  - Court Reform, Simplified Court Structure, 1955-1958 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 22)
  - Court Reform, Judiciary Article, 1958-1959 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 23)
  - Court Reform, Pamphlets and News Clippings, 1954-1959 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 24)
  - Court Reform, Pamphlets and News Clippings, 1961-1967 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 25)
  - Court Reform, Pamphlets, 1971-1998 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 26)
  - Court Reform, Adoptions and Family Court, 1963-1965; 1968 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 27)
  - Court Reform, Court Structure and Judiciary Article, 1965-1967 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 28)
  - Court Reform, Judicial Resource Kits, 1969 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 29)
  - Court Reform, Criminal Courts, 1973-1978 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 30)
  - Court Reform, Court Merger and Merit Selection of Judges, 1978-1986 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 31)
  - Court Reform, New York State Legislative Acts Regarding Court Merger and Merit Selection of Judges, 1981; 1983 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 32)
  - Court Reform, Fund for Modern Courts, 1980-1981 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 33)
  - Court Reform, Fund for Modern Courts, 1982 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 34)
  - Court Reform Newspaper Clippings, 1981-1983 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 35)
  - Court Reform Fund for Modern Courts, 1983-1986 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 36)
  - Court Reform, Fund for Modern Courts, 1989-1992 (Box 16 (5-Study and Action), Folder 37)
  - Court Reform, Fund for Modern Courts, 1992-1997 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 1)
  - Court Reform, Merit Selection of Judges, 1994 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 2)
  - Criminal Justice, Alternatives to Incarceration Committee, 1991-1994 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 3)
  - Criminal Justice, Alternatives to Incarceration reports, 1992 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 4)
  - Criminal Justice, Women in Prison Project, 1991 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 5)
  - Criminal Justice, Women in Prison Project, 1991-1993 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 6)
  - Criminal Justice, Conference, 1992 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 7)
  - Criminal Justice, Directory, 1993 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 8)
  - Criminal Justice, Newsletters, 1985-1993 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 9)
  - Criminal Justice, Balancing Justice, 1999 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 10)
  - Criminal Justice, Balancing Justice, 1999-2000 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 11)
  - Cross-Endorsement Study, 1982-1983 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 12)
  - Crossroads Project, 1993-1995 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 13)
  - Districting, 1964-1967 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 14)
  - Earth Day Lobby Day, 1995 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 15)
  - Education Resource Kit, 1965 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 16)
  - Electoral College Study, 1968-1969 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 17)
  - Electoral College Study, 1969-1970 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 18)
  - Environmental Quality Bond Act, 1972; 1990 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 19)
  - Equal Rights Amendment in the United States, 1972; 1975-1983 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 20)
  - Equal Rights Amendment in New York State, 1975 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 21)
  - Federal Budget Study, 1953 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 22)
  - Financing Education, 1958-1961 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 23)
  - Financing Education, 1962; 1967; 1969 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 24)
  - Financing Education, 1972-1980 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 25)
  - Financing Education, 1981-1983; 1985-1986 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 26)
  - Financing Education, 1995-1997 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 27)
  - Financing Public Higher Education, 1996; 1998-1999 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 28)
  - Financing the Federal Government Study, 1985-1986 (Box 17 (5-Study and Action), Folder 29)
  - Government, Loyalty-Security Program, 1956; 1968 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 1)
  - Government, Positions LWVNYS Issues, 1978-1997 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 2)
  - Government, Representative, 1971-1985 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 3)
  - Great Decisions, 1976-1985 (not inclusive) (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 4)
  - Gun Control, 1991 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 5)
  - Hazardous Waste, 1984 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 6)
  - Hazardous Waste, Household, 1997 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 7)
  - Health Care, 1983-1985 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 8)
  - Health Care Reform, 1993-1994 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 9)
  - Human Resources, Development, 1964-1966 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 10)
  - Human Resources, Civil Rights, 1963-1965 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 11)
  - Human Resources, Economic Opportunity, 1963-1970 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 12)
  - Human Resources, Education and Welfare, 1975-1978; 1982; 1983 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 13)
  - Human Resources, Social Policy, 1980-1983 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 14)
  - Human Resources, Hunger and Volunteer Workforce, 1987-1988; 1990 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 15)
  - Human Resources, Meeting Basic Human Needs, 1988 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 16)
  - Human Resources, Social Welfare, 1997 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 17)
  - Industry, Undated (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 18)
  - Initiatives and Referendum, 1977-1979 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 19)
  - International Relations, Local Survey on World Trade, 1954 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 20)
  - International Relations, Foreign Economic Aid, Trade, United Nations, 1961-1964 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 21)
  - International Relations, Foreign Economic Aid, Trade, United Nations, 1965-1967 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 22)
  - International Relations, Foreign Economic Aid, Trade, United Nations, 1968-1970 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 23)
  - International Relations, Foreign Economic Aid, Trade, United Nations, 1971-1972 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 24)
  - International Relations, Trade, 1973-1974 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 25)
  - International Relations, Foreign Economic Aid and Trade, 1975-1979 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 26)
  - International Relations, United Nations and Arms Control, S.A.L.T. II, 1978-1979 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 27)
  - International Relations: United Nations and Arms Control, S.A.L.T. II, 1980-1981 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 28)
  - International Relations: Foreign Economic Aid, 1985 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 29)
  - International Relations: News Clippings, 1984 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 30)
  - International Relations: News Clippings, 1985 (Box 18 (5-Study and Action), Folder 31)
  - International Relations: Trade, 1991-1995 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 1)
  - International Relations: Trade, News Clippings, 1996 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 2)
  - International Relations: Trade, News Clippings and Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 3)
  - International Relations and National Security, 1984-1985 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 4)
  - International Relations and National Security, 1985 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 5)
  - International Relations and National Security, 1986-1987 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 6)
  - International Relations and National Security, News Clippings, 1981-1983 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 7)
  - International Relations and National Security, News Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 8)
  - International Relations and National Security, News Clippings, 1986 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 9)
  - Job Training, 1984 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 10)
  - Legislative Action, 1943; 1952-1956 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 11)
  - Legislative Action, 1966-1967 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 12)
  - Legislative Action, 1968 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 13)
  - Legislative Action, 1969 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 14)
  - Legislative Action, 1970-1971; 1972 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 15)
  - Legislative Action, 1974-1976; 1978 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 16)
  - Legislative Action, 1981-1982; 1984-1986 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 17)
  - Legislative Action, 1987-1988 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 18)
  - Legislative Action, 1989 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 19)
  - Legislative Action, 1990 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 20)
  - Legislative Action, 1990-1992 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 21)
  - Legislative Action, 1994-1997 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 22)
  - Legislative Action, 1998 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 23)
  - Legislative Action, 1999 (Box 19 (5-Study and Action), Folder 24)
  - Legislative Action Guides, 1971-1975; 1978 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 1)
  - Litigation involving LWV, 1972-1975; 1977-1978 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 2)
  - Lobby/Observer Corps Training Session, 1994 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 3)
  - Lobby/Observer Corps Training Session, 1995 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 4)
  - Lobby/Observer Corps Training Session, 1996 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 5)
  - Lobby/Observer Corps Training Session, 1997 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 6)
  - Lobbying Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 7)
  - Lobbying Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 8)
  - Lobbying Correspondence, Foreign Economic Aid, 1975; 1979 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 9)
  - Lobbying Correspondence, Government, 1975-1976; 1979-1980 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 10)
  - Lobbying Correspondence, Housing, 1977-1979 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 11)
  - Lobbying Correspondence, Judicial, 1976-1979 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 12)
  - Lobbying Correspondence, Natural Resources, 1975; 1978-1979; 1987 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 13)
  - Medicare, 1998 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 14)
  - National Security Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 15)
  - National Security Committee, 1983 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 16)
  - National Security, Arms Control Study and Survey, 1982-1983 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 17)
  - National Security, Military Policy Objectives Study, 1983-1984 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 18)
  - National Security, MX Missile Program, 1985 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 19)
  - National Security, News Clippings, 1983 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 20-21)
  - National Security, News Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 22)
  - Natural Resources, Energy, 1974-1982 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 23)
  - Natural Resources, Environmental Quality, 1972; 1975-1980 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 24)
  - Natural Resources, Environmental Quality, 1981-1986 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 25)
  - Natural Resources, Environmental Quality, 1987-1994 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 26)
  - Natural Resources, Environmental Quality, 1995-1997 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 27)
  - Natural Resources, Land Use, 1971-1975; 1979 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 28)
  - Natural Resources, 1997-1998 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 29)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, Proposed, 1957 (Box 20 (5-Study and Action), Folder 30)
  - NYS Constitutional Convention, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 1)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, Convention Kits and LWV Statements, 1966-1967 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 2)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, Reports and "Vote NO" Campaign, 1967 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 3)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, Newsletters, Pamphlets, News Clippings, 1967 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 4)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, Financial Study of Public Authorities, 1967 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 5)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention Official Text of the Proposed Constitution of the State of New York and Your Proposed New Constitution: Text, Abstract, and Highlights, 1967 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 6)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, Constitution Making Procedures, 1968; 1969 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 7)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, Convention News Service, 1967 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 8)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, Reviews, 1973; 1994 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 9)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, Temporary State Commission on Constitutional Revision, Meeting Presentation and Minutes, 1993-1995 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 10)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, Temporary State Commission on Constitutional Revision, Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1995-1997 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 11)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, Briefing Book Draft Chapters, 1993 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 12-14)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention The New York State Constitution: A Briefing Book, Temporary State Commission on Constitutional Revision, 1994 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 15)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, Interim Report of the Temporary State Commission of Constitutional Revision, 1994 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 16)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, Final Report of the Temporary State Commission of Constitutional Revision, 1995 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 17)